<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Welcome to SketchyRecall</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="rules">SketchyRecall Rules</string>
    <string name="rules_title">How to Play SketchyRecall:</string>
    <string name="rules_p">Minimum 4 players.  \nPlay will rotate with a different player as the "describer" each turn and the rest as "drawers".  The describer will study an image silently for a short time, then describe the image to the drawers without looking at the image.  During this time, the drawers should attempt to recreate the image being described to them.  Drawers may ask the describer questions.  When time is up, drawers show their drawings.  The describer should privately mark the player who\'s image they believe to be most correct BEFORE looking at the image again.  Then, everyone may see the original image and drawers privately vote for which drawing besides their own is the most accurate.  Scoring: the player the describer chose gets 1 point.  The player with the most drawer votes gets 1 point (each get one if there is a tie).  If the player with the most drawer votes is also the one chosen by the describer, give a point to the describer for giving an accurate description.  Rotate describer and hit "Play Again".</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="image">A random AI generated image for participants to try to draw.</string>
    <string name="placeholder_timer">0:12 seconds</string>
    <string name="placeholder_x">x</string>
    <string name="reveal">Reveal Image</string>
    <string name="again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="study">Study</string>
    <string name="draw">Draw</string>
    <string name="times_up">Time\'s Up!</string>
    <string name="back_button">return to homepage</string>
    <string name="game">SketchyRecall</string>
    <string name="rules_button">Rules</string>
    <string name="zero_timer_text">0 seconds left</string>
    <string name="timer_text">Remaining Seconds</string>
    <string name="study_rules">You have 30 seconds to study the image before you are allowed to describe it.</string>
    <string name="draw_rules">You have 2.5 minutes to describe the image to the drawers, while they draw.</string>
    <string name="times_up_rules">After the Describer has marked their choice, Click the button below.</string>
    <string name="reveal_rules">"Drawers look at the image and vote for which drawing is most accurate.  "</string>
    <string name="waiting">Please wait for an image to load...</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to Sketchy Recall!</string>
</resources>